

# **ALEXANDRA CANGE**

### **JUNIOR DATA SCIENTIST**

+49 174 7453284

 $\checkmark$ 

alexandracange@gmail.com

2

Berlin, Germany

in

LinkedIn



Github



<u>Portfolio</u>

### PROFILE

Ex-Operations Manager, I decided to make a big career change and to start in Tech. After 5 years in Operations and exploring my leadership and organisational skills, I wanted to do something more related to datas and IT. That where my journey began. I am now a student in a Data Sciences Bootcamp at WBS School.

### **EDUCATION**

### **DATA SCIENCES**

WBS CODING SCHOOL, BERLIN

09.2022 -01.2023

- Project based
- Practice oriented
- collaborative coding training

### **BACHELOR OF ART**

PUBLIC UNIVERSITY, ORLEANS

09.2013 -07.2016  Languages, International Business and Commerce, International Management

## **EXPERIENCE**

### **VIU EYEWEAR, MUNICH**

04.2021 -05.2022

### SENIOR OPERATIONS MANAGER

- Directed and oversaw staff of 25+ employee, designing schedules to meet the needs of the department as well as the needs of employees.
- Implemented a new inventory analysing system resulting saving 20% of spent time.

### 01.2020 -03.2021

# SWQ (Shipping, Warehouse, Quality Control)

### MANAGER

- Maintained detailed records of stocks, incoming goods and shipments.
- Evaluated productivity, implemented new processes and tracking processes systems resulting a better organisation and KPIs.

### 01.2019 -

#### SHIPPING SUPERVISOR

12.2019

- Supervised up to 10 shipping employees.
- Ensured all outbound orders are processed within 1.5 day.

#### 10.2017 -

#### **OPERATIONS SPECIALIST**

12.2018

• Assisted to company goals and operational excellence.

#### KIABI, ORLEANS

06.2016 -09.2016

### **INTERNSHIP ASSISTANT MANAGER**

 Analysed with Excel and reported on the NPS to management and director.

# **TECH SKILLS**

- Python
- SQL
- Tableau
- AWS
- Machine Learning
- Web-Scrapping
- API
- Data Visualisation
- HTML
- CSS

# **SOFT SKILLS**

- Fast Learning
- Problem Solving
- Adaptability
- Stress Tolerance
- Leadership

# **LANGUAGES**

- French C2/Native
- English C1
- German B2

Berlin.